// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be classified as an auxiliary to trade?",
    answer: "Mining",
    options: [
      "Mining",
      "Insurance",
      "Warehousing",
      "Transport"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be classified as an objective of business?",
    answer: "Investment",
    options: [
      "Investment",
      "Productivity",
      "Innovation",
      "Profit earning"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The industries which provide support services to other industries are known as",
    answer: "Tertiary industries.",
    options: [
      "Primary industries",
      "Secondary industries",
      "Commercial industries",
      "Tertiary industries."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the broad categories of industries covers oil refinery and sugar mills?",
    answer: "Secondary",
    options: [
      "Primary",
      "Secondary",
      "Tertiary",
      "None of them"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Business risk is not likely to arise due to ?",
    answer: "Good management",
    options: [
      "Changes in government policy",
      "Good management",
      "Employee dishonesty",
      "Power failure"
    ]
    
  },
  {
 numb: 6,
 question: "Find the odd one",
 answer: "Praying in a church",
 options: [
    "Teaching in a school",
    "Practicing in a court",
    "Praying in a church",
    "Running a hotel"
  ]  

  },
  
    {
 numb: 7,
 question: "The occupation in which people work for others and get remunerated in return is known as",
 answer: "Employment",
 options: [
    "Business",
    "Employment",
    "Profession",
    "None of them"
  ]  

  },
    {
 numb: 8,
 question: "Which of the following does not characterize business activity?",
 answer: "Salary or wages",
 options: [
    "Production of goods and services",
    "Presence of risk",
    "Sale or exchange of goods and services",
    "Salary or wages"
  ]  

  },
      {
 numb: 9,
 question: "Complete the following equation: Commerce = ____+ Aids to trade",
 answer: "Trade",
 options: [
    "Service",
    "Industry",
    "Business",
    "Trade"
  ]  

  },
      {
 numb: 10,
 question: "Extraction of coal is an example of industries.",
 answer: "",
 options: [
    "Genetic",
    "Construction",
    "Extractive",
    "Manufacturing"
  ]  

  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

   //  {
    // numb: 7,
   //  question: "Your Question is Here",
  //  answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
   //  options: [
   //    "Option 1",
    //   "option 2",
    //  "option 3",
    //   "option 4"
   //  ]
   //},
];
